Ben Myers

UCLA undergraduate pursuing B.S. in Mathematics with three years of customer service experience, one year of educational experience, and five years of programming experience. Involved in software development, management, and business growth.

Personal involvements include UCLA Chorale, UCLA Sigma Eta Pi, Bruin Entrepreneurs, and the UCLA Founder's Club. Interests include AI; cryptocurrency; proof computation; DJ'ing; music/video production; choral singing; VC.

+1 561-374-4627 benl.myers01@gmail.com benlmyers.com github.com/benlmyers

Technical Skills Languages

Python Swift JavaScript C++Java HTML + CSS C# Rust

Environments and Tools

SwiftUI, UIKit Unity, Unreal React, RN, Vue JavaX, Swing Blender Adobe PS, AI, PR Git + Github FL Studio + Logic

Education

Alexander W. Dreyfoos School of the Arts University of California, Los Angeles H.S. Diploma, 2020 | 4.0 GPA | 5.037 HPA | 1510 SAT | 33 ACT B.S. Mathematics, 2024 | 3.483 Major GPA

Experience

Co-Founder and CTO

Jun 2022 - Present

Poppin Technologies - Full-time

www.ioinpoppin.com

- · Built mobile app, data structure, and UI/UX from ground-up with a modern Swift tech stack in three months.
- Scaled app by 25,000% to 18,000 MAU with 500+ organic user-hosted events, breaking Top 100 on App Store.
- · Improved end-user experience with Firebase integration, online payments, and ticketing.
- · Led web/mobile development team of 4 with, dynamic content/linking, and payment integration.

Founder and CEO Jan 2021 - Present

Flowductive - Part-time

www.flowductive.com

- Brought Flowductive to Startup UCLA Summer Accelerator, raising \$5,000, as the youngest solo founder.
- Self-built 5 iterations of a iOS + macOS productivity app; web landing page; and 3 open-source Swift packages.
- · Raised and managed company's socials, internship cohort of 18; and captured interest from industry-leading VCs.
- · Represented at UCLA startup programs, including events hosted by Bruin Labs and Bruin Entrepreneurs.

Nov 2020 - Present iOS Developer www.yatco.com

Yatco - Full-time

- Improved web SEO for a yachting MLS website with 600+ visitors/day in traffic.
- Parsed 2000+ yacht builder data objects from sites into JSON using Python scripts.
- · Developed leading-edge mobile Charter/Consumer application, disrupting a \$10 billion market.

Dec 2021 - Feb 2022 iOS Developer

Edvora - Internship

www.edvora.com

- · Stabilized and widened the mobile device compatibility of a global SaaS education solution.
- · Improved the quality and scalability of the future of Ed-tech in education, technology, finance, and enterprise.

Code Sensei Jan 2020 - Apr 2021 Code Ninias - Part-time www.codeninjas.com

- Taught kids ages 7-14 how to code in languages such as Swift, JavaScript, Lua, and Python.
- · Directed, supervised, and taught children coding skills during several themed summer camps.
- · Hosted and assisted with routine online code learning sessions over Zoom.

Customer Service Agent

Dec 2016 - Jun 2020

Publix - Part-time

www.publix.com

- · Worked as an item bagger, then a cashier, then a customer service agent, for one year each.
- · Recognized 7 times for outstanding customer service and continually achieved "Exceeding Expectations" and "Role Model" marks in biannual performance evaluations.
- Promoted twice for demonstrated leadership and proactiveness.